<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress.com" created="2016-08-25 03:02"-->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>Gary Ditsch</title>
	<link>http://garyditsch.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 03:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
	<language></language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://wordpress.com/</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://garyditsch.com</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>490632</wp:author_id><wp:author_login><![CDATA[gditsch]]></wp:author_login><wp:author_email><![CDATA[garyditsch@gmail.com]]></wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[garyd]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[Gary]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Ditsch]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>

	<wp:category><wp:term_id>118743</wp:term_id><wp:category_nicename>bootcamp</wp:category_nicename><wp:category_parent></wp:category_parent><wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Bootcamp]]></wp:cat_name></wp:category>

	<generator>http://wordpress.com/</generator>
<image>
		<url>http://s2.wp.com/i/buttonw-com.png</url>
		<title>Gary Ditsch</title>
		<link>http://garyditsch.com</link>
	</image>
		
	<item>
		<title>My perspective as I begin 12 weeks of development bootcamp</title>
		<link>http://garyditsch.com/2016/08/17/my-perspective-as-i-begin-12-weeks-of-development-bootcamp/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 16:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>gditsch</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://garyditsch.com/?p=426</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[One of my favorite documentaries is <a href="http://www.merufilm.com/" target="_blank">Meru</a>. It tells the story of Jimmy Chin, Conrad Anker and Renan Ozturk as they attempt to climb the Shark’s Fin on Mount Meru. After a failed attempt in 2008, the story returns to the United States where the three climbers make sense of their motivations to climb the mountain again. During this time, Renan Ozturk has a major accident that puts his ability to walk again into question. This reality did not deter Renan’s desire to get health and strong enough to make another attempt on Meru with his two friends Jimmy and Conrad.

In their story, there was a pivotal decision that needed to be made by Jimmy and Conrad. They had to decide if they would feel comfortable making a summit attempt with Renan, even if he was able get back to normal strength. Would they ever be able to trust his abilities in the way they did prior to his accident?

There are those moments in life that you can look back on that appear to be clearly pivotal moments. When I look back on the past 37.95 years here are a few of those moments that I can identify with hindsight: (In chronological order)
<blockquote>
<ul>
<ol>1. Transferring to O’Neill Public High School my senior year of high school</ol>
<ol>2. Deciding to go to college, then attending the University of Nebraska - Lincoln (this was not always a given in my mind)</ol>
<ol>3. Choosing exercise science as my major (who knew studying exercise was a possibility?)</ol>
<ol>4. Moving to Kentucky to attend graduate school</ol>
<ol>5. Working as a health educator for Teller County Public Health and the Steps to a Healthier US program</ol>
<ol>6. Getting married</ol>
<ol>7. Deciding to move back to Kentucky and ultimately choosing to call Lexington our home</ol>
<ol>8. Making the decision to work full-time on Endurance Base Camp (although EBC name actually came later)</ol>
<ol>9. Joining Retrofit and not working on Endurance Base Camp</ol>
</ul>
</blockquote>
As I review the list, there are a few themes: education, location and work are important variables on the list. In this reflection, I am highlighting those events because of the adventures that I am getting ready to start. If I would make another list, I would include the many relationships and friendships that I have made. Meeting certain individuals and developing those relationships over the years would easily have a bigger impact on life than what education, job or place I have chosen.

But today I’m focused on education, occupation and location. Why? The answer is because this week is the beginning of my next adventure which will impact all three of these areas of my life.

<strong>Education:</strong>

Today I will meet the nine other individuals who are starting the <a href="https://www.awesomeincu.com/bootcamp/">Awesome Inc U’s Web Developer Bootcamp</a>. Starting the bootcamp was a fairly large decision for me, as it is a 12 week full time commitment. I anticipate that for the duration of the program, things will be intense. The accelerated pace of learning is going to be both a challenge and exciting experience.

<strong>Occupation:</strong>

In 2001 I made my first attempt at starting a company that brought allied health services online. My vision at the time was to bring exercise, nutrition, athletic training and general health (nursing) professionals together, then offer those services to individuals who were looking to optimize their health. That experience was a total failure in every sense of the word. I realized that I did not understand nearly as much about business as I thought I did. I also discovered that it would be challenging to build businesses on the web if I did not understand how the web operated. That is when I started to learn various web development technologies. I learned the basics. Since that time I have played around with html, css and some php. Things were much different in 2001 then they are today. Today you can create well designed and beautiful websites without any programming knowledge.

The journey since that time has been a lot of fun. I have learned at every turn that being at the intersection between technology and an individual’s health, fitness and wellness goals is where I am the most happy. This is an exciting intersection to work and play.

When I take a look at the current state of this intersection, I get excited about the advancement in sensor, monitoring and diagnostic technologies and the corresponding data collection from those technologies. That data needs places to go, whether it’s your electronic health records or an app that shows the mapping of your last bike ride. Finally, that data needs to have a purpose. It needs to be able to inform your physician, improve your medical care, notify allied health professionals, allow you to optimize your own nutrition or fitness program, document baseline health metrics and monitor changes in health status over time. In reality, the uses of that data feels like an endless road of possibilities.

I try and live in the second and third stages of that process. I like to focus on where data goes and how to intelligently use that data to improve the individual’s health, fitness and performance.

<strong>Education + Occupation:</strong>

My goal in pursuing the education from the bootcamp is to improve my personal skill set so I can perform better. I would consider myself an expert in the areas of health, fitness and performance. I also believe I have an excellent sense for using data to optimize decision making, as it relates to those domains. What I hope to learn through this experience is how to more effectively store, manipulate and display that data. Having worked with others who were very talented and experienced in those areas the past 4.5 years at Retrofit, I realized that had a growing desire to develop those skills myself. While I have made progress over the past couple years, I am looking forward to the opportunity to focus on nothing but developing those skills for the next 12 weeks.

<strong>Location:</strong>

What does location have to do with this reflection? It was some time ago that I realized that I had become less engaged in the local community. The only real engagement I had with Lexington was through the run group I support each fall and spring. While that provided some sense of involvement, I had a strong desire to become more involved. To better understand how I could participate more in the local startup environment, I contacted Nick Such from <a href="https://www.awesomeinc.org/">AwesomeInc</a>. That meeting lead to me joining the membership, which was effectively a weekly tutoring program for coding. It also lead me to participate in the <a href="http://www.cherubfund.org/">Cherub Fund</a>. At times, I would find myself at a <a href="http://www.5across.org/">5 Across competition</a>. AwesomeInc has been a major catalyst for individuals and companies that are interested in pursing high tech locally.

This past weekend, I was fortunate to join a group of local entrepreneurs and the folks from AwesomeInc on a retreat to the Smokey Mountains. It allowed me time to reflect on many of the thoughts I’ve shared here, but also confirmed my desire to grow my investment of time and energy into this community. At the moment, my passion projects to facilitate this is my new podcast <a href="http://www.activelexington.com/">Active Lexington</a> and facilitating the <a href="http://www.centralkentuckygrandprix.com/">Central Kentucky Grand Prix Series</a>. By participating in the bootcamp, I will be investing in myself but also in the program AwesomeInc has made available and ultimately in Lexington.

Until the next summit attempt:

In Meru, the time that was spent by Jimmy Chin, Conrad Anker and Renan Ozturk between their failed summit attempt in 2008 and their successful 2011 summit was not wasted time. It was time that each of the climbers needed to take to be fully prepared prior to making that second attempt. I am trying to take a similar perspective to the next 12 weeks. It is going to be intense, stressful, rewarding, satisfying and likely full of moments of failure. However, I know that the effort will be worthwhile, because the world of health, fitness, performance, data and technology only gets bigger each month - and I will be even more equipped to traverse those routes when I am finished.]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>426</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-08-17 12:29:29</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-08-17 16:29:29</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>my-perspective-as-i-begin-12-weeks-of-development-bootcamp</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="bootcamp"><![CDATA[Bootcamp]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[490632]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[427]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[25880287237]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>geo_public</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>SmokeyClimb</title>
		<link>http://garyditsch.com/2016/08/17/my-perspective-as-i-begin-12-weeks-of-development-bootcamp/2016-08-13-16-32-47/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 16:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>gditsch</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://garyditschdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/2016-08-13-16-32-47.jpg</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[Climbing Chimeny Rock in the Smokey Mountains]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>427</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-08-17 12:28:28</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-08-17 16:28:28</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>2016-08-13-16-32-47</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>426</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:attachment_url>https://garyditschdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/2016-08-13-16-32-47.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attached_file</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/422/42698448/files/2016/08/2016-08-13-16-32-47.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:5:{s:5:"width";i:1280;s:6:"height";i:960;s:4:"file";s:95:"/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/422/42698448/files/2016/08/2016-08-13-16-32-47.jpg";s:5:"sizes";a:0:{}s:10:"image_meta";a:12:{s:8:"aperture";s:3:"2.4";s:6:"credit";s:0:"";s:6:"camera";s:9:"iPhone SE";s:7:"caption";s:0:"";s:17:"created_timestamp";s:10:"1471105967";s:9:"copyright";s:0:"";s:12:"focal_length";s:4:"2.15";s:3:"iso";s:2:"50";s:13:"shutter_speed";s:18:"0.0034129692832765";s:5:"title";s:0:"";s:11:"orientation";s:1:"1";s:8:"keywords";a:0:{}}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Web Development Bootcamp - Day 1</title>
		<link>http://garyditsch.com/2016/08/23/web-development-bootcamp-day-1/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>gditsch</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://garyditsch.com/?p=432</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">The first day of bootcamp is complete and here are a few things that I took away with me:</p>
<p class="p1">1. Changing programming languages creates syntax issues for me right now. I anticipate this to become less of a challenge as I become more fluent in the languages.</p>
<p class="p1">I have been using python for some data analysis. I also build the Central Kentucky Grand Prix site on python / Django. This level of comfort seemed to disappear in the coding challenges. We could choose javascript or python to solve the problem. I started in python but switched to javascript. I have been studying javascript so much the past 10 days that I kept messing up the python syntax. I switched over to javascript and just dealt with the fact that I don’t fully know all the methods available, YET!</p>
<p class="p1">2. Git (and Github) is an amazing tool. However, learning how to optimize the workflow when working with a team of people on a project is going to take some time.<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>I’ve been using git for awhile on my Central Kentucky Grand Prix project. The big difference is that I’m the only person working on that project (well other than the person I hired to build an iOS app), so I do not need to worry too much about other programmers changing code. This will take time.</p>
<p class="p1">3. Working in teams is great! Almost all of my web development projects over the years have been done on my own. I’ve hired a contractor every once in awhile, but primarily done in isolation.<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>Having a second pair of eyes on a task or problem clearly accelerates the time span it takes to get through a problem.</p>
<p class="p1">4. We had a lunch presentation on ‘learning to learn’.<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>Over the next 12 weeks, I’ll have the opportunity to test many of those ideas!</p>
<p class="p1">Main subjects and skills learned today: HTML, CSS, git, GitHub, 3<span class="s1"><sup>rd</sup></span> party tools to help build sites (google forms, youtube, paypal, google maps).</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>432</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-08-23 07:52:55</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-08-23 11:52:55</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>web-development-bootcamp-day-1</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="bootcamp"><![CDATA[Bootcamp]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[26065074608]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>geo_public</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[433]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[490632]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Bootcamp Day 1</title>
		<link>http://garyditsch.com/2016/08/23/web-development-bootcamp-day-1/img_2539/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 11:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>gditsch</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://garyditschdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_2539.jpg</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>433</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-08-23 07:52:15</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-08-23 11:52:15</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>img_2539</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>432</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:attachment_url>https://garyditschdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_2539.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_image_alt</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Computer on desk]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:5:{s:5:"width";i:4032;s:6:"height";i:3024;s:4:"file";s:84:"/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/422/42698448/files/2016/08/img_2539.jpg";s:5:"sizes";a:0:{}s:10:"image_meta";a:12:{s:8:"aperture";s:3:"2.2";s:6:"credit";s:0:"";s:6:"camera";s:9:"iPhone SE";s:7:"caption";s:0:"";s:17:"created_timestamp";s:10:"1471861315";s:9:"copyright";s:0:"";s:12:"focal_length";s:4:"4.15";s:3:"iso";s:2:"25";s:13:"shutter_speed";s:5:"0.025";s:5:"title";s:0:"";s:11:"orientation";s:1:"1";s:8:"keywords";a:0:{}}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attached_file</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/422/42698448/files/2016/08/img_2539.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Web Development Bootcamp - Day 2</title>
		<link>http://garyditsch.com/2016/08/24/web-development-bootcamp-day-2/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>gditsch</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://garyditsch.com/?p=436</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p class="p1">The day started out pretty frustratingly, as I could not complete a fairly simple challenge. There was some issues with the website we were using, which threw me off, however I mentally got stuck and couldn’t get unstuck. It would have been ideal to have changed tasks, maybe even getting up for 5 minutes. I did not do take that advice. I continued into a 30 minute stagnation of thought. The day got much better after that first 1.5 hours.</p>
<p class="p1">The day was primarily spent diving into CSS concepts. My comfort level with CSS is pretty high, so this material was good review. The other thing that I appreciated was having discussions on why somethings worked . There are coding decisions that I’ve used in the past that work, but I never knew the logic behind the code. A perfect example is getting something to center on a page using:</p>
<p class="p1">.container {
<span class="Apple-converted-space">   m</span>argin: 0 auto;
}</p>
<p class="p1">I have also have challenges in the past to get this to work, but now I understand that a container that you want to float should have a defined width. The container that encloses that container also works best when it has a defined width.</p>
<p class="p1">Another topic that we covered, that I have used for years but struggled with at times and only get to work through brute force and trial and error is floating an object. Getting things to position themselves via float, is still something that takes some trial and error, but at least I have a little better understanding.</p>
<p class="p1">The other thing that I realize even more after the day’s work, is that I appreciate Twitter Bootstrap even more. I have been using it for any of the CSS work that I have had to do the past year. It really does make life so much easier than building the style sheet from scratch. We haven’t got into Bootstrap yet, but it’s on the schedule.</p>
<p class="p1">Here are a few resources I found helpful for the work today:</p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">- One: <a href="http://superuser.com/questions/536768/how-to-shift-a-block-of-text-to-the-right-left-in-sublime-text-2">How to tab text in Sublime</span></a></span></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s1">- Two: <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/css/css_align.asp"><span class="s2">CSS align</span></a></span></p>
<p class="p1">- Three: <a href="http://www.w3schools.com/css/css_float.asp">CSS float</a></p>
<p class="p1">At the end of classes today we set up our Ruby environments, as we are going to start working with Jekyll next.</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>436</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-08-24 07:57:31</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-08-24 11:57:31</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>web-development-bootcamp-day-2</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="bootcamp"><![CDATA[Bootcamp]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[490632]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_thumbnail_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[439]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>geo_public</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[26099908361]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>CSS Day at Bootcamp</title>
		<link>http://garyditsch.com/2016/08/24/web-development-bootcamp-day-2/img_2539-2/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>gditsch</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://garyditschdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_25391.jpg</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>437</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-08-24 07:56:58</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-08-24 11:56:58</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>img_2539-2</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>436</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:attachment_url>https://garyditschdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_25391.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:5:{s:5:"width";i:4032;s:6:"height";i:3024;s:4:"file";s:85:"/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/422/42698448/files/2016/08/img_25391.jpg";s:5:"sizes";a:0:{}s:10:"image_meta";a:12:{s:8:"aperture";s:3:"2.2";s:6:"credit";s:0:"";s:6:"camera";s:9:"iPhone SE";s:7:"caption";s:0:"";s:17:"created_timestamp";s:10:"1471861315";s:9:"copyright";s:0:"";s:12:"focal_length";s:4:"4.15";s:3:"iso";s:2:"25";s:13:"shutter_speed";s:5:"0.025";s:5:"title";s:0:"";s:11:"orientation";s:1:"1";s:8:"keywords";a:0:{}}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attached_file</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/422/42698448/files/2016/08/img_25391.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_image_alt</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Working on CSS]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>IMG_2546</title>
		<link>http://garyditsch.com/2016/08/24/web-development-bootcamp-day-2/img_2546/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 12:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>gditsch</dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://garyditschdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_2546.jpg</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>439</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2016-08-24 08:59:03</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2016-08-24 12:59:03</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>img_2546</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>436</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<wp:attachment_url>https://garyditschdotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/08/img_2546.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attached_file</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/422/42698448/files/2016/08/img_2546.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_metadata</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:5:{s:5:"width";i:4032;s:6:"height";i:3024;s:4:"file";s:84:"/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/422/42698448/files/2016/08/img_2546.jpg";s:5:"sizes";a:0:{}s:10:"image_meta";a:12:{s:8:"aperture";s:3:"2.2";s:6:"credit";s:0:"";s:6:"camera";s:9:"iPhone SE";s:7:"caption";s:0:"";s:17:"created_timestamp";s:10:"1472025146";s:9:"copyright";s:0:"";s:12:"focal_length";s:4:"4.15";s:3:"iso";s:2:"25";s:13:"shutter_speed";s:17:"0.033333333333333";s:5:"title";s:0:"";s:11:"orientation";s:1:"1";s:8:"keywords";a:0:{}}}]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
